http://www.ihoptallahassee.org/privacypolicy

Popular topics
ArticlesLonger-form articles covering the deep topics of the Bible and Christian lifestyle.
WorshipWorship includes knowing God truly and responding from the heart by treasuring Him.
PrayerPrayer to God includes our praises, confessions, thanksgivings, and requests.
The BibleGod has revealed Himself to humanity in a book that we can access whenever we desire.
Photo DocumentaryEvents and special features showcased through large beautiful photography.
Updated 2/1/2016
This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us.
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
New Testament Bible Reading Plan
Read through the New Testament in 50 days November 12th–December 31st, 2020.
View Reading Plan
Copyright © 2020 Hilltop House of Prayer. Site by Ink Blot Media Group | Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions
